Some types of light
Can also disturb me very much.
When something feels boring or hard
I easily disappear in completely different thoughts.
When it is not clear what to do
I often become completely paralyzed
And do nothing.
When one has ADHD it is
Usually it goes great
to focus when something
Is fun and interesting.
I have no energy and press
All the time on the snooze button.
It can be incredibly hard
To sit still when you have ADHD.
It feels like one constantly
Has ants in Brallan.
It may feel hard to keep up
The energy for a whole day.
It is common to man
Finds some different strategies
To spike.
One usually split up the diagnosis of ADHD